# Matt Millard

# Bartender / Server

Applying for the position of Seasonal Taproom Associate

### Contact



613 223 9371



Matt.Richie.Millard@gmail.com



instagram.com/\_mattmillard



21535 Seven Hills Road Vankleek Hill

#### Interests

Photography

Programming

Travel

Skiing

Music Production

# Education

Bachelor's Degree Music Production SAE Byron Bay, Australia 2008 - 2011

HND Audio Engineering Perth, Scotland 2006 - 2008

# Availability

Looking for 3 days/week. Available any day and time.

# About

I have a great attitude and a friendly personality that makes me very easy to work with. I take great pride in providing professional and personable service to customers and hold a decade of experience working within the hospitality industry. My beer knowledge is strong and I believe I would be a great addition to your team at Beaus.

# Experience

#### Bartender

Bar Swift | Soho, London, UK | 2018 - 2020

Very popular and established cocktail bar located in the bustling streets of Soho. Independently owned and operated by award-winning bartenders.

- Contributed to and collaborated towards cocktail menus.
- Worked dispense bar station 5 nights/week.
- Responsible for weekly bar prep and bar setup.
- Always willing to worked floor shifts and take charge of bar back duties.
- Responsible for weekly beer line cleaning duties, organising inventory and the cutting of block ice.

#### Head Bartender

Bar Laurel | Ottawa | 2016 - 2018

A Spanish tapas bar with a heavy focus on creative, seasonal and classic cocktails with an extensive offering of low intervention wines, Spanish ciders, and local sour beers.

## Bartender

Panda & Sons | Edinburgh, Scotland | 2014 - 2016

Owned and operated by some of Scotland's most celebrated bartenders. Panda & Sons, located in the heart of Edinburgh, is an award-winning, high volume basement speakeasy.

# General Manager & Barista

Sand Dollar Café | Aberdeen, Scotland | 2011 - 2014

My mum Suzi's café located on the bonnie beachfront of Aberdeen, Scotland. A turn and burn style café, serving up freshly cooked breakfast, brunch, lunch and delicious coffee.